second-to-none.com 2013-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Legal Notice | Second To None

### Privacy Policy

At Second To None we are committed to protecting your privacy. When you visit our web site, our web server automatically logs your domain and notes what pages you view. The only personal identifying information we collect from you is what you provide on a voluntary basis, such as contact, survey, or application information. This information can include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. 

We assure you that we will use the information we collect about you only to help us improve services to you, to answer your questions and to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you. You may permanently opt-out of these promotional offers by emailing us at [webmaster@second-to-none.com](mailto:webmaster@second-to-none.com), or calling us at +1 734.302.8400. 

We do not sell your personal information to anyone. Although, we will occasionally share information with business partners to administer the products and services we provide, we do not divulge any of your personal information to these parties. 

BY USING THIS WEB SITE YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. Second To None stands behind the following privacy policy. Please read on for details. 

######## What information do we collect?

When you visit our web site, our web server automatically logs your domain and notes what pages you view. The only personal identifying information we collect from you is what you provide on a voluntary basis, such as contact, survey, or application information. This information can include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. 

Your computer reaches us via a particular IP (Internet Protocol) address. This can tell us things like what part of the world you're connecting from, or what Internet service provider you are using. 

Your browser offers "cookies" that, if you allow their use, store bits of data on your computer about your visit to our site. This data includes which features of our site you like best. When you revisit the Second To None web site, these cookies enable us to customize our web site content according to your preferences. However, cookies do not give us any personally identifying information about you. The only way we get personal information identifying you is if you give it to us. 

######## What do we do with the information we collect?

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages, to customize the content for each individual visitor, to complete evaluations and surveys requested by our clients, and to contact visitors for recruiting and marketing purposes. All information will be stored as securely as possible while maintaining the ability for authorized employees to access this information when required. 

######## Who can use the information we collect and how?

Any information we gather is kept confidential. We will never willfully disclose identifiable information about our clients, evaluators, or visitors to any third party or mailing list without first receiving authorization. 

Second To None does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to anyone without your consent. 

######## How do we protect the personal information we collect?

Second To None uses encryption technology to keep your personal information safe and to protect it against unauthorized access. Your information—including your name, address, e-mail address and phone number—is encrypted using a secure server so that information cannot be read as it travels to our computer system. Once we receive your information we store it on a server that isn't accessible from the Internet. 

If you feel more comfortable doing so, you are welcome to call in your personal information. You may reach us at +1 734.302.8400. 

######## How do you correct, update, or remove your personal information?

To change, correct, or remove information you previously submitted to us, email or call us at: 

  * ###### Mystery Shoppers/Secret Shoppers

  * +1 734.302.8444

  * ###### Clients/Visitors

  * webmaster@second-to-none.com
  * +1 734.302.8400

######## What is our web site acceptable use policy and legal notice?

We provide a web site Acceptable Use Policy and Legal Notice to guide the conduct of our visitors regarding privacy and appropriate behavior when using our web site. 

######## What is our privacy policy if you link to a third-party web site?

When you click on hyperlinks that take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy statement whenever interacting with any Web site. 

######## What happens to your personal information in a business transfer?

While we do not anticipate it, every business nowadays should plan for the possibility that it might sell certain or all of its assets to another company, or that it might buy certain assets of another company. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the business assets that is transferred. Please read the section How do we notify you of changes? to understand what your options are. 

######## How do we notify you of changes?

If at any time we decide to use your personally identifiable information in any way that is different from what we stated at the time it was collected, then we will notify you using the email address you provided. You will have a choice about whether or not you want us to use your information in this different way. Be assured, unless you consent otherwise, we will use your information in accordance with the privacy policy that was in effect at the time we collected your information from you. 

######## Your consent.

By visiting and using our web site, you consent to our collection and use of this information. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. If we alter our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. 

######## Tell us what you think!

We want to know what you think, and welcome any questions or comments you may have about privacy. Please send us an email at [webmaster@second-to-none.com](mailto:webmaster@second-to-none.com). 

######## Copyright and Trademark Notice & Use of Intellectual Property 

The Second To None, Inc. website (www.second-to-none.com), and all of its contents, including but not limited to articles, other text, photographs, images, illustrations, graphics, Second To None® logos, titles, characters, names, graphics and button icons (collectively "Intellectual Property"), are protected by copyright, trademark and other laws of the United States, as well as international conventions and the laws of other countries. The terms "Brand Authenticity", "Holistic Customer Experience Management", "Holistic CEM", "Six Degrees of Practical", "Transformative Customer Advocacy", "Next Level Brand Performance", "Every Interaction Counts", "Catapult", and "Moving You From Data-Driven To Data-Informed" are trademarks of Second To None, Inc. and considered Intellectual Property. The Intellectual Property is owned or controlled by Second To None, Inc.

You may not, and agree that you will not, reproduce, download, license, publish, enter into a database, display, modify, create derivative works from, transmit, post, distribute or perform publicly by any means, method, or process now known or later developed, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, use on another computer-related environment, transfer or sell any Intellectual Property, information, or products obtained from or through this Second To None® website, in whole or in part, without the express written permission of Second To None®. Other trademarks, service marks, product names and company names or logos appearing on this Second To None® website that are not owned by Second To None® may not be used without express permission from their owners. Additionally, unless otherwise expressly permitted, websites may not hyperlink to any page beyond the homepage of this Second To None® website, or frame this Second To None® website, or any web page or material herein, nor may any entity include a hyperlink to any aspect of the Second To None® website in an email for commercial purposes, without the express written permission of Second To None®. 

######## Copyright Infringement

Second To None® respects the intellectual property rights of third parties, and complies with the terms of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) regarding such rights. By submitting any material or photographs through this Second To None® website, you are granting permission to have this material posted on this Second To None® website, and are representing that you are the rightful owner of the submitted material, and that no one else may claim rights to this material. Second To None® reserves the right to remove access to infringing material. Such actions do not affect or modify any other rights Second To None® may have under law or contract.
